Andara Puteri Syalsabella

Surabaya | linkedin.com/in/andarass| +6282245340303 | andarass18@gmail.com

SUMMARY

Fresh graduate State University of Surabaya, majoring in Informatics Engineering, with practical experience gained through a student-centric, growth-oriented internship. Recognized for adaptable, leadership, creative thinking, and problem solver. Has been competence in the area of Graphic Designer, Illustrator, Video Editor, Full-Stack Developer, Microsoft Word, Microsoft PowerPoint & Microsoft Excel.

EDUCATION

ED C CHITION	
Universitas Negeri Surabaya	Surabaya
Informatics Engineering	September 2020 – August 2024

CERTIFICATE

Universitas Negeri Surabaya	Surabaya
• Certificates:	
Participation in "Peranan Artificial Intelligence & Analisis Data"	10 November 2020
Participation in "Burma: Militer, Demokrasi, dan Geo-politik Kawasan Asia Tenggara'	° 01 April 2021
Participation in "Media Sosial untuk Usaha Anda"	04 April 2021
Participation in "Penerapan Kebijakan Pajak Digital Sebagai	05 April 2021
Upaya Stimulus Ekonomi Negara Melalui Optimalisasi Pajak di Indonesia"	
Participation in "Webinar Nasional: Menjernihkan Hati, Melawan Radikalisme"	30 April 2021
Participation in "Duta Perubahan Perilaku (SATGAS Covid-19)"	30 April 2021
Participation in "Kupas Tuntas Sistem Bea Cukai dan	28 Juni 2021
Strategi Mencegah Kecurangan Praktik Ekspor Impor Barang"	
Participation in "Kelas TOEFL Online"	14-23 July 2021
Participation in "Social Media and Self Expression Through Art"	31 July 2021
Participation in "Mempelajari Sejarah, untuk Mengukir Sejarah"	17 August 2021
Participation in "Adopting Healthy Lifestyle to Fight Climate Change"	13 August 2021
Participation in "Get to Know Entrepreneurship: Ways To Start"	18 August 2021
Participation in "Make Slicing Design with Flutter"	07-15 August 2021
\mathbf{J}	06-07 November 2021
dan ber-Jiwa Kepemimpinan"	
Participation in "Sosialisasi Program Kreativitas Mahasiswa"	01 March 2022
Participation in "Kesetaraan Genre Disabilitas dalam Perspektif Agama"	08 August 2022
Participation in "Eksistensi Gen Z Untuk Membangun Bisnis Kreatif	11 September 2022
di Era Revolusi Society 5.0"	
Participation in "Kesetaraan Genre Disabilitas dalam Perspektif Agama"	08 August 2022
Participation in "Free Intensive Bootcamp: Microsoft Excel - Basic Microsoft Excel held by MySkill x Deloitte"	01 August 2024
Participation in "MySkill Short Class: Influencer Marketing"	02 August 2024

SMAN 1 Kertosono

• Certificates:

3rd place in "BI Corner Challenge 2 (BICC2)"	09-11 October 2018
Finalist in "ILPC 2020 (Informatics Logical Proramming Competition 2020)"	16-18 Januari 2020

WORK EXPERIENCE

Aksamedia (PT Aksamedia Mulia Digital)	Hybrid (Online-Offline)
Digital Creator	February 2024 – July 2024

- Video Editor.
- Creative Designer.

JAPFA Comfeed Tbk

Hybrid (Online-Offline)

Staff Assistant in TI Development-Consumer Go Direct

January 2023 – May 2023

- Internship.
- Full-Stack Developer.

Freelancer Kertosono

Community Development

February 2018 – April 2021

- Photography, Videography and Video Editor at wedding.
- Designed raw logo.
- Designed banner and pamphlet.

SMAN 1 Kertosono

Multimedia Designer

June 2017 - March 2020

- Taken pictures & videos activities organized by the school.
- Designed charter of organization.
- Cameraman and video editor of SMAN 1 Kertosono's anniversary.

ORGANIZATION EXPERIENCE

Team Creative SMAN 1 Kertosono

Kertosono

June 2017 – March 2020

- Staff of the Education DepartmentMember of Team Creative SMAN 1 Kertosono.
- Documentating every activity held in SMAN 1 Kertosono.
- Carried out activities related to the SMAN 1 Kertosono schedule.
- Coordinator and contributor of designing logo, phamplet, schedule, banner and etc (related to edit) of SMAN 1 Kertosono's 55th anniversary.
- Coordinator and contributor of designing logo, phamplet, schedule, banner and etc (related to edit) of SMAN 1 Kertosono's 56th anniversary.

English Club SMAN 1 Kertosono

Work From Home

Staff of the Education Departement

August 2019 – March 2020

- Contribution being an active member.
- Help to organized the countdown schedule.
- Promoting English Club activity.
- Inform the news and open recruitment of English Club.

SKILLS & INTERESTS

Skills: Project Management | Leadership | Web Developer | Front-End Designer | Design Graphic | Photography | Video Editor | Illustrator | Microsoft Word | Microsoft PowerPoint | Microsoft Excel

Interests: Writing, Design, Photography, Videography, Psychology, Music Composer